{
  "jokes": [
    {
      "question": "Which body part does a programmer know best?",
      "answer": "ARM",
      "upvotes": 172,
      "downvotes": 52,
      "id": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Relationship status?",
      "answer": "I'll leave the relations to the database.",
      "upvotes": 15,
      "downvotes": 107,
      "id": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "How do you get the code for the bank vault?",
      "answer": "You checkout their branch.",
      "upvotes": 151,
      "downvotes": 25,
      "id": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "How did the developer announce their engagement?",
      "answer": "They returned true!",
      "upvotes": 133,
      "downvotes": 168,
      "id": 4
    },
    {
      "question": "Why did the security conscious engineer refuse to pay their dinner bill?",
      "answer": "Because they could not verify the checksum.",
      "upvotes": 137,
      "downvotes": 32,
      "id": 5
    },
    {
      "question": "What do you call a busy waiter?",
      "answer": "A server.",
      "upvotes": 39,
      "downvotes": 163,
      "id": 6
    },
    {
      "question": "What do you call an idle server?",
      "answer": "A waiter.",
      "upvotes": 183,
      "downvotes": 55,
      "id": 7
    },
    {
      "question": "How many Prolog programmers does it take to change a lightbulb?",
      "answer": "Yes.",
      "upvotes": 7,
      "downvotes": 14,
      "id": 8
    },
    {
      "question": "What diet did the ghost developer go on?",
      "answer": "Boolean",
      "upvotes": 54,
      "downvotes": 120,
      "id": 9
    },
    {
      "question": "Why was the developer unhappy at their job?",
      "answer": "They wanted arrays.",
      "upvotes": 163,
      "downvotes": 52,
      "id": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "Why was the function sad after a successful first call?",
      "answer": "It didn’t get a callback.",
      "upvotes": 7,
      "downvotes": 183,
      "id": 11
    },
    {
      "question": "Why did the angry function exceed the callstack size?",
      "answer": "It got into an Argument with itself",
      "upvotes": 80,
      "downvotes": 78,
      "id": 12
    },
    {
      "question": "Whats the object-oriented way to become wealthy?",
      "answer": "Inheritance",
      "upvotes": 92,
      "downvotes": 137,
      "id": 13
    },
    {
      "question": "Why did the developer ground their kid?",
      "answer": "They weren't telling the truthy",
      "upvotes": 127,
      "downvotes": 12,
      "id": 14
    },
    {
      "question": "What did the array say after it was extended?",
      "answer": "Stop objectifying me.",
      "upvotes": 40,
      "downvotes": 29,
      "id": 15
    },
    {
      "question": "Where did the parallel function wash its hands?",
      "answer": "Async",
      "upvotes": 183,
      "downvotes": 18,
      "id": 16
    },
    {
      "question": "Why did the functions stop calling each other?",
      "answer": "Because they had constant arguments.",
      "upvotes": 153,
      "downvotes": 134,
      "id": 17
    },
    {
      "question": "What's the second movie about a database engineer called?",
      "answer": "The SQL.",
      "upvotes": 103,
      "downvotes": 45,
      "id": 18
    },
    {
      "question": "Why doesn't Hollywood make more Big Data movies?",
      "answer": "NoSQL.",
      "upvotes": 95,
      "downvotes": 62,
      "id": 19
    },
    {
      "question": "What did the spider do on the computer?",
      "answer": "Made a website!",
      "upvotes": 46,
      "downvotes": 144,
      "id": 20
    },
    {
      "question": "What did the computer do at lunchtime?",
      "answer": "Had a byte!",
      "upvotes": 167,
      "downvotes": 89,
      "id": 21
    },
    {
      "question": "What does a baby computer call his father?",
      "answer": "Data!",
      "upvotes": 82,
      "downvotes": 12,
      "id": 22
    },
    {
      "question": "Why did the computer keep sneezing?",
      "answer": "It had a virus!",
      "upvotes": 116,
      "downvotes": 11,
      "id": 23
    },
    {
      "question": "What is a computer virus?",
      "answer": "A terminal illness!",
      "upvotes": 138,
      "downvotes": 135,
      "id": 24
    },
    {
      "question": "Why was the computer freezing?",
      "answer": "It left its Windows open!",
      "upvotes": 119,
      "downvotes": 97,
      "id": 25
    },
    {
      "question": "Why was there a bug in the computer?",
      "answer": "Because it was looking for a byte to eat?",
      "upvotes": 172,
      "downvotes": 143,
      "id": 26
    },
    {
      "question": "Why did the computer squeak?",
      "answer": "Because someone stepped on its mouse!",
      "upvotes": 58,
      "downvotes": 127,
      "id": 27
    },
    {
      "question": "What do you get when you cross a computer and a life guard?",
      "answer": "A screensaver!",
      "upvotes": 131,
      "downvotes": 18,
      "id": 28
    },
    {
      "question": "Where do all the cool mice live?",
      "answer": "In their mousepads!",
      "upvotes": 199,
      "downvotes": 52,
      "id": 29
    },
    {
      "question": "What do you get when you cross a computer with an elephant?",
      "answer": "Lots of memory!",
      "upvotes": 67,
      "downvotes": 77,
      "id": 30
    },
    {
      "question": "How do programming pirates pass method parameters?",
      "answer": "Varrrrarrrgs.",
      "upvotes": 133,
      "downvotes": 40,
      "id": 31
    },
    {
      "question": "How do programming shepherds count their flock?",
      "answer": "With lambda functions",
      "upvotes": 51,
      "downvotes": 157,
      "id": 32
    },
    {
      "question": "What airline do developers prefer when they're in a rush?",
      "answer": "Delta.",
      "upvotes": 2,
      "downvotes": 155,
      "id": 33
    },
    {
      "question": "How did pirates collaborate before computers ?",
      "answer": "Pier to pier networking.",
      "upvotes": 36,
      "downvotes": 181,
      "id": 34
    },
    {
      "question": "Why don't bachelors like Git?",
      "answer": "Because they are afraid to commit.",
      "upvotes": 62,
      "downvotes": 132,
      "id": 35
    },
    {
      "question": "Why was the developer's family upset with them at dinner?",
      "answer": "They forgot to git squash before going home",
      "upvotes": 105,
      "downvotes": 48,
      "id": 36
    },
    {
      "question": "What did JavaScript call his son?",
      "answer": "JSON!",
      "upvotes": 184,
      "downvotes": 121,
      "id": 37
    },
    {
      "question": "What did the proud React component say to its child?",
      "answer": "I've got to give you props",
      "upvotes": 54,
      "downvotes": 9,
      "id": 38
    },
    {
      "question": "What did the server say to his client who was having a bad day?",
      "answer": "Everything's going to be 200",
      "upvotes": 79,
      "downvotes": 43,
      "id": 39
    },
    {
      "question": "Why did the developer go broke?",
      "answer": "Because they used up all their cache",
      "upvotes": 183,
      "downvotes": 97,
      "id": 40
    },
    {
      "question": "Are computers dangerous?",
      "answer": "Nah, they don't byte. They just nibble a bit.",
      "upvotes": 142,
      "downvotes": 40,
      "id": 41
    },
    {
      "question": "How did the mafioso kill the Node server?",
      "answer": "Tie await to it and let it async.",
      "upvotes": 14,
      "downvotes": 10,
      "id": 42
    },
    {
      "question": "You know what the best thing about booleans is?",
      "answer": "Even if you are wrong, you are only off by a bit.",
      "upvotes": 111,
      "downvotes": 182,
      "id": 43
    },
    {
      "question": "Why do UPS drivers get nervous when their internet is unstable?",
      "answer": "Because they might lose packets.",
      "upvotes": 107,
      "downvotes": 54,
      "id": 44
    },
    {
      "question": "Why couldn’t the user update a file on a shared server?",
      "answer": "They didn’t have the write permissions",
      "upvotes": 101,
      "downvotes": 66,
      "id": 45
    },
    {
      "question": "What do you do when you can't understand your husband's behavior?",
      "answer": "man man",
      "upvotes": 107,
      "downvotes": 88,
      "id": 46
    },
    {
      "question": "What do you call a doctor who fixes websites?",
      "answer": "A URLogist",
      "upvotes": 12,
      "downvotes": 125,
      "id": 47
    },
    {
      "question": "How many developers does it take to change a light bulb?",
      "answer": "None. It's a hardware issue",
      "upvotes": 14,
      "downvotes": 189,
      "id": 48
    },
    {
      "question": "Why do programmers always mix up Halloween and Christmas?",
      "answer": "Because 31 OCT == 25 DEC",
      "upvotes": 102,
      "downvotes": 96,
      "id": 49
    },
    {
      "question": "Why do kayakers make bad programmers?",
      "answer": "Because they're afraid of waterfall.",
      "upvotes": 33,
      "downvotes": 49,
      "id": 50
    },
    {
      "question": "What are computers' favorite snacks?",
      "answer": "Microchips, phish sticks, and cookies. But just a few bytes of each.",
      "upvotes": 31,
      "downvotes": 161,
      "id": 51
    },
    {
      "question": "What do computers love to do at the beach?",
      "answer": "Put on some spam block for protection so they can safely surf the net while catching some .WAVs!",
      "upvotes": 16,
      "downvotes": 173,
      "id": 52
    },
    {
      "question": "What do you call a computer that sings?",
      "answer": "A-dell.",
      "upvotes": 78,
      "downvotes": 5,
      "id": 53
    },
    {
      "question": "What's a compiler developer's favorite spice?",
      "answer": "Parsley.",
      "upvotes": 135,
      "downvotes": 15,
      "id": 54
    },
    {
      "question": "When do front end developers go out to eat?",
      "answer": "On their lunch `<br>`.",
      "upvotes": 27,
      "downvotes": 161,
      "id": 55
    },
    {
      "question": "How do you help JS errors?",
      "answer": "You `console` them!",
      "upvotes": 6,
      "downvotes": 16,
      "id": 56
    },
    {
      "question": "Why don't parents teach their kids about regular expressions?",
      "answer": "Because they don't want them playing with matches",
      "upvotes": 54,
      "downvotes": 85,
      "id": 57
    },
    {
      "question": "Why didn't the `<div />` get invited to the dinner party?",
      "answer": "Because it had no class!",
      "upvotes": 148,
      "downvotes": 83,
      "id": 58
    },
    {
      "question": "Why aren't cryptocurrency engineers allowed to vote?",
      "answer": "Because they're miners!",
      "upvotes": 134,
      "downvotes": 94,
      "id": 59
    },
    {
      "question": "Why did the constant break up with the variable?",
      "answer": "Because they changed.",
      "upvotes": 137,
      "downvotes": 53,
      "id": 60
    },
    {
      "question": "Why did the database administrator leave his wife?",
      "answer": "She had one-to-many relationships.",
      "upvotes": 141,
      "downvotes": 23,
      "id": 61
    },
    {
      "question": "What did the Class say in court when put on trial?",
      "answer": "I strongly object!",
      "upvotes": 126,
      "downvotes": 115,
      "id": 62
    },
    {
      "question": "Why do Java developers wear glasses?",
      "answer": "Because they don't C#!",
      "upvotes": 182,
      "downvotes": 154,
      "id": 63
    },
    {
      "question": "What are the three hardest problems in computer science?",
      "answer": "Naming things and off-by-one errors",
      "upvotes": 17,
      "downvotes": 47,
      "id": 64
    },
    {
      "question": "What did the fruit basket say to the developer?",
      "answer": "I hope you're ready for some pear programming!",
      "upvotes": 196,
      "downvotes": 173,
      "id": 65
    },
    {
      "question": "How does a sysadmin keep a fire going?",
      "answer": "They rotate the logs.",
      "upvotes": 47,
      "downvotes": 94,
      "id": 66
    },
    {
      "question": "I love you and I only love you. Does that turn you on?",
      "answer": "AND GATE: No.",
      "upvotes": 40,
      "downvotes": 168,
      "id": 67
    },
    {
      "question": "Why do all HTML emails get blocked?",
      "answer": "Because they are all `<span />`.",
      "upvotes": 12,
      "downvotes": 53,
      "id": 68
    },
    {
      "question": "What did the process say after working in an infinite loop all day?",
      "answer": "I need a break.",
      "upvotes": 5,
      "downvotes": 34,
      "id": 69
    },
    {
      "question": "An Agent died unexpectedly. How was the crime solved?",
      "answer": "By looking at the Stack Trace.",
      "upvotes": 93,
      "downvotes": 191,
      "id": 70
    },
    {
      "question": "Why did the document store go out of business?",
      "answer": "It had NoSQL.",
      "upvotes": 151,
      "downvotes": 108,
      "id": 71
    },
    {
      "question": "Why can't SQL and NoSQL Developers date one other?",
      "answer": "Because they don't agree on relationships.",
      "upvotes": 109,
      "downvotes": 115,
      "id": 72
    },
    {
      "question": "Why is Python like the Soviet Union?",
      "answer": "Because it has no private fields",
      "upvotes": 194,
      "downvotes": 90,
      "id": 73
    },
    {
      "question": "Where did the API go to eat?",
      "answer": "To the RESTaurant",
      "upvotes": 135,
      "downvotes": 88,
      "id": 74
    },
    {
      "question": "Why shouldn't you trust Matlab developers?",
      "answer": "Because they're always plotting something.",
      "upvotes": 131,
      "downvotes": 73,
      "id": 75
    },
    {
      "question": "Why did the developer have to quit smoking?",
      "answer": "Because they couldn't afford to pay the new syntax.",
      "upvotes": 170,
      "downvotes": 146,
      "id": 76
    },
    {
      "question": "How does a programmer open a jar for their significant other?",
      "answer": "They install Java",
      "upvotes": 53,
      "downvotes": 51,
      "id": 77
    },
    {
      "question": "What did the psychic say to the developers?",
      "answer": "I see dev people.",
      "upvotes": 40,
      "downvotes": 189,
      "id": 78
    },
    {
      "question": "Where does the pirate stash all of their digital treasures?",
      "answer": "RAR",
      "upvotes": 188,
      "downvotes": 10,
      "id": 79
    },
    {
      "question": "What is React's favorite movie genre?",
      "answer": "Suspense",
      "upvotes": 178,
      "downvotes": 188,
      "id": 80
    },
    {
      "question": "Why couldn't the React component understand the joke?",
      "answer": "Because it didn't get the context.",
      "upvotes": 93,
      "downvotes": 147,
      "id": 81
    },
    {
      "question": "What did XHR say to AJAX when it thought it was being a Mean Girl?",
      "answer": "Stop trying to make fetch happen!",
      "upvotes": 13,
      "downvotes": 73,
      "id": 82
    },
    {
      "question": "What was Grace Hopper's favorite car?",
      "answer": "VW Bug",
      "upvotes": 160,
      "downvotes": 197,
      "id": 83
    },
    {
      "question": "What is a pirate's favorite programming language?",
      "answer": "You'd think it was R, but a pirate's first love is Objectively C.",
      "upvotes": 9,
      "downvotes": 57,
      "id": 84
    },
    {
      "question": "Why did the programmer come home crying?",
      "answer": "His friends were always boolean him.",
      "upvotes": 146,
      "downvotes": 74,
      "id": 85
    },
    {
      "question": "What PostgreSQL library should Python developers use for adult-oriented code?",
      "answer": "psycoPG13",
      "upvotes": 44,
      "downvotes": 159,
      "id": 86
    },
    {
      "question": "What do you call a beverage that is 75% Root Beer, and 75% Ice Cream?",
      "answer": "A Float",
      "upvotes": 132,
      "downvotes": 87,
      "id": 87
    },
    {
      "question": "What accommodations did the JavaScript developer request at the hotel?",
      "answer": "A room with a Vue.",
      "upvotes": 165,
      "downvotes": 96,
      "id": 88
    },
    {
      "question": "Where do developers drink?",
      "answer": "The Foo bar",
      "upvotes": 188,
      "downvotes": 46,
      "id": 89
    },
    {
      "question": "Why was the engineer upset when the bartender served them `1` shot of whiskey?",
      "answer": "Because they thought they ordered a double.",
      "upvotes": 88,
      "downvotes": 18,
      "id": 90
    },
    {
      "question": "Why do assembly programmers need to know how to swim?",
      "answer": "Because they work below C level.",
      "upvotes": 122,
      "downvotes": 128,
      "id": 91
    },
    {
      "question": "Who used the internet before it was cool?",
      "answer": "Httpsters",
      "upvotes": 111,
      "downvotes": 153,
      "id": 92
    },
    {
      "question": "What kind of computer can hold a musical note?",
      "answer": "A Dell.",
      "upvotes": 125,
      "downvotes": 154,
      "id": 93
    },
    {
      "question": "Why did the web developer always go to the wrong hotel room?",
      "answer": "They were in room 301.",
      "upvotes": 177,
      "downvotes": 37,
      "id": 94
    },
    {
      "question": "How do you stop a web developer stealing your stuff?",
      "answer": "Write 403 on it.",
      "upvotes": 38,
      "downvotes": 109,
      "id": 95
    },
    {
      "question": "Why are machine learning models so fit?",
      "answer": "Because they do weight training.",
      "upvotes": 18,
      "downvotes": 197,
      "id": 96
    },
    {
      "question": "Why did Gargamel shut down the internet?",
      "answer": "Because he didn't want people **SMURFING** the web!",
      "upvotes": 33,
      "downvotes": 40,
      "id": 97
    },
    {
      "question": "What did the command line die of?",
      "answer": "A Terminal illness.",
      "upvotes": 32,
      "downvotes": 164,
      "id": 98
    },
    {
      "question": "Did you hear what the clumsy cryptographer did to their password?",
      "answer": "Made a hash of it.",
      "upvotes": 36,
      "downvotes": 168,
      "id": 99
    },
    {
      "question": "Why are keyboards always working so hard?",
      "answer": "Cause they have two shifts!",
      "upvotes": 81,
      "downvotes": 51,
      "id": 100
    },
    {
      "question": "What are clouds made of?",
      "answer": "Mostly linux servers.",
      "upvotes": 56,
      "downvotes": 196,
      "id": 101
    },
    {
      "question": "Why did Tom Selleck never git commit anything?",
      "answer": "Because he thought he mustache his work.",
      "upvotes": 133,
      "downvotes": 194,
      "id": 102
    },
    {
      "question": "How does Mr. Potato Head (dev edition 0.0.1) remove his mustache?",
      "answer": "git stache pop",
      "upvotes": 53,
      "downvotes": 126,
      "id": 103
    },
    {
      "question": "Why can't you use 'Soup' as your password?",
      "answer": "Because it isn't `stroganoff`",
      "upvotes": 153,
      "downvotes": 58,
      "id": 104
    },
    {
      "question": "Why do developers use mechanical keyboards?",
      "answer": "To strongly type their code.",
      "upvotes": 93,
      "downvotes": 172,
      "id": 105
    },
    {
      "question": "What is a developer's favorite country song?",
      "answer": "Hello World - by Lady Antebellum",
      "upvotes": 138,
      "downvotes": 2,
      "id": 106
    },
    {
      "question": "Why was nobody given food at the developer conference?",
      "answer": "It was a serverless function!",
      "upvotes": 138,
      "downvotes": 64,
      "id": 107
    },
    {
      "question": "Why did the developer cancel their dinner plans?",
      "answer": "They were unable to fulfil peer dependencies",
      "upvotes": 0,
      "downvotes": 100,
      "id": 108
    },
    {
      "question": "Why did the functional programmer finally move out of their house?",
      "answer": "For(e) closure",
      "upvotes": 116,
      "downvotes": 168,
      "id": 109
    },
    {
      "question": "How do JavaScript developers break up?",
      "answer": "They always promise to callback",
      "upvotes": 75,
      "downvotes": 17,
      "id": 110
    },
    {
      "question": "Why do developers mixup Terminals and Polygraphs?",
      "answer": "Because they both can see a lie (CLI)",
      "upvotes": 29,
      "downvotes": 174,
      "id": 111
    },
    {
      "question": "Did you hear about the programmer that was scared of IDEs?",
      "answer": "They retreated back into their shell",
      "upvotes": 132,
      "downvotes": 175,
      "id": 112
    },
    {
      "question": "What do you call optimistic front-end developers?",
      "answer": "Stack half-full developers.",
      "upvotes": 146,
      "downvotes": 93,
      "id": 113
    },
    {
      "question": "Have you heard the one about the Corduroy pillow?",
      "answer": "It's making HEADLINES!",
      "upvotes": 135,
      "downvotes": 61,
      "id": 114
    },
    {
      "question": "Hey officer! How did the hackers escape?",
      "answer": "No idea. They just ransomware.",
      "upvotes": 199,
      "downvotes": 66,
      "id": 115
    },
    {
      "question": "Why can’t data engineers become hat makers?",
      "answer": "They can only guarantee two thirds of a CAP!",
      "upvotes": 46,
      "downvotes": 125,
      "id": 116
    },
    {
      "question": "How did the hippie learn about database transactions?",
      "answer": "By taking ACID",
      "upvotes": 174,
      "downvotes": 165,
      "id": 117
    },
    {
      "question": "Why is it called the Dark Ages?",
      "answer": "There were a lot of KNIGHTS!",
      "upvotes": 51,
      "downvotes": 186,
      "id": 118
    },
    {
      "question": "What did the Network Administrator say when they caught a nasty virus?",
      "answer": "It hurts when IP",
      "upvotes": 184,
      "downvotes": 134,
      "id": 119
    },
    {
      "question": "Which programming language is the shortest?",
      "answer": "HTML. Because it doesn't have a neck between its `<head>` and `<body>`.",
      "upvotes": 182,
      "downvotes": 117,
      "id": 120
    },
    {
      "question": "What good can come of 2989 witches casting a hex?",
      "answer": "None, it is always 0xBAD",
      "upvotes": 71,
      "downvotes": 55,
      "id": 121
    },
    {
      "question": "Did you hear about the witch who was off by two when casting a hex?",
      "answer": "They failed to make the target DEAD and made them DEAF instead!",
      "upvotes": 195,
      "downvotes": 193,
      "id": 122
    },
    {
      "question": "Why do Front-End Developers eat lunch alone?",
      "answer": "Because, they don't know how to join tables.",
      "upvotes": 119,
      "downvotes": 54,
      "id": 123
    },
    {
      "question": "What advice do you give to a JS developer who has never played baseball?",
      "answer": "Try catch.",
      "upvotes": 84,
      "downvotes": 101,
      "id": 124
    },
    {
      "question": "Got any funny DNS jokes?",
      "answer": "Yeah, but it may take 24 hours to get it.",
      "upvotes": 109,
      "downvotes": 5,
      "id": 125
    },
    {
      "question": "Why were A & B so frustrated?",
      "answer": "Because they couldn’t cd…",
      "upvotes": 13,
      "downvotes": 7,
      "id": 126
    },
    {
      "question": "Where do programmer dad's store their jokes?",
      "answer": "In a dad-a-base.",
      "upvotes": 197,
      "downvotes": 154,
      "id": 127
    },
    {
      "question": "Why do Websockets make the best therapists?",
      "answer": "They are always listening.",
      "upvotes": 87,
      "downvotes": 136,
      "id": 128
    },
    {
      "question": "What kind of image saved the day?",
      "answer": "The HERO image!",
      "upvotes": 6,
      "downvotes": 1,
      "id": 129
    },
    {
      "question": "Why do programmers prefer dark mode?",
      "answer": "Because light attracts bugs!",
      "upvotes": 22,
      "downvotes": 6,
      "id": 130
    },
    {
      "question": "Does this vaccine contain a microchip?",
      "answer": "I don't know for sure, but it must be ARM based.",
      "upvotes": 166,
      "downvotes": 195,
      "id": 131
    },
    {
      "question": "How do you make a 4D Printer?",
      "answer": "Take a 3D printer and give it some time",
      "upvotes": 72,
      "downvotes": 148,
      "id": 132
    },
    {
      "question": "How do front end devs like their brownies?",
      "answer": "GUI",
      "upvotes": 162,
      "downvotes": 73,
      "id": 133
    },
    {
      "question": "What do hackers do on a boat?",
      "answer": "Phishing.",
      "upvotes": 152,
      "downvotes": 52,
      "id": 134
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the most used language in programming?",
      "answer": "Profanity",
      "upvotes": 34,
      "downvotes": 136,
      "id": 135
    },
    {
      "question": "Why couldn't the HTML list be trusted?",
      "answer": "There were LI's everywhere",
      "upvotes": 37,
      "downvotes": 50,
      "id": 136
    },
    {
      "question": "What do you call a bee that lives in America?",
      "answer": "A USB",
      "upvotes": 158,
      "downvotes": 181,
      "id": 137
    },
    {
      "answer": "bahaba",
      "question": "dumb",
      "id": 435932.7396290691
    },
    {
      "answer": "dsfsdf",
      "question": "dfsdf",
      "id": 831127.5738113998
    },
    {
      "answer": "Not funny at all",
      "question": "Not Funny Joke",
      "id": 248116.9253873059
    },
    {
      "answer": "",
      "question": "",
      "id": 105010.70028085982
    },
    {
      "answer": "sdf",
      "question": "sdf",
      "id": 17175.120981710836
    },
    {
      "answer": "sdfsdf",
      "question": "sdfsdf",
      "id": 131242.12523790015
    },
    {
      "answer": "dsfsdf",
      "question": "dfsdf",
      "id": 145819.56039987112
    }
  ]
}